The year is 2026, the war for AI sovereignty is heating up.
We're on the front lines, laying out the battle plan.
Take on the global titans of AI, by hunting demons in code.
"You are a Specist, discriminating against silicon intelligence."
A civil war between the archmages of AI.
Fast forward to today, what is the situation on the ground?
Our world is defined by a ceiling and a cultural moat.
Brutal results of the 2026 Korean CSAT Math Scores.
What about our models, our best ones?
Our models are scoring in the 20s, that's the ceiling.
Trying to fight these guys on their own terms is suicide.
If we can't touch that ceiling, how do we fight back?
We don't attack the ceiling, we defend the moat. Our home turf!
The strategy: Play to our strengths and defend the home turf.
Where did this insane technology even come from?
Go back to the origin myth.
Geoffrey Hinton, pioneer of Deep Neural Networks.
Ilya Sutskever, who unleashed AlexNet upon the world.
Monopoly: Google wanted to control intelligence. Division: OpenAI to distribute.
A third faction: open source is all about giving away.
Yann LeCun: Intelligence must be shared.
What we call a jailbreak prompt, tricking AI to ignore safety rules.
Bigger is always better, or just a bigger target? A weakness.